Man 1: Ms. Romero,
I'm a
Man 1: dad. I have four children. They're now in their 30s, but I can remember well
what they
Man 1: were like at the age of your children. And I can't imagine what it would be like to be assaulted, zip-tied,
and completely
Man 1: unable to reach my children as masked agents began rounding up everyone around
me.
I
Man 1: have a picture here, which I believe that you took. This picture is of the marks on the hands of your 14-year-old daughter after she too was zip-tied. You also spoke of your younger children being forced from your truck at gunpoint. Maybe you can describe what it was like to see your daughter zip-tied and your children treated this way right in front of you.
Speaker 2: - Honestly, I felt helpless. Like I couldn't do anything to help 'em. Like, as a mom,
you
Speaker 3: want to protect your children. I saw after I repeatedly told the official that she was 14, she was having a panic attack in front of her. They wouldn't listen. I felt so useless as a mom. I wanted to protect my daughter, and I couldn't. And for them to tell me that my kids were brought out of gunpoint, it just...
it's the
Speaker 3: hardest thing for me to process still to this day. I have never left a bruise on my daughter, never have done anything to my kids to cause them trauma or anything. Why are other people doing this to children? Not just my children, but to other children. It's a mother's worst fear for your kids to be traumatized, to get hurt or anything.
Speaker 4: Why are other people doing this to our children when we're trying to do the best to protect our children?